ANOTHER ONE
This happened to me when
I was on the business trip.
There was an academic conference,
so all hotels were booked up.
I managed to get a twin room in this hotel.
It's sad using a twin room by myself.
Yes.
I had a bad feeling about the room.
Here it is.
I'm going to get some sleep.
I'm going to sleep.
Namu Amida Buddha
Hai.
Let's go!
That's enough.
Maybe the receptionist knew something?
Perhaps in that room...
a high school basketball coach
hung himself.
They didn't confirm this.
The End
THE MEN IN BLACK
Minoru! What happened to you?
Who are they?
Tell me who they are!
That can't be.
They must be Frisbees.
They are real.
The last one turned out be an airplane.
Look!
Not again...
I just took something much more amazing.
I bet this is genuine.
I'm home!
Hi!
What have you done, Minoru?
What?
Come off it. Strange people came down.
They said they knew you.
I don't know.
These huge guys were dressed all in black.
Completely black.
Who are they?
I really don't know.
Give us some drink!
Minoru!
What's this?
Mom!
Who did that?
What are you talking about?
My room is a mess.
I don't know. It's your fault.
Liar.
Cut it out!
Hello.
It's me.
Are you sure?
Ok, I'll come right away.
Thank you.
Toshihiko, I had a call
from Bermuda magazine.
They're going to publish my picture.
They want to speak to me now.
Minoru didn't come back.
Thank you.
Not at all.
His parents asked the police to search for him.
Goodbye.
Yokoyama
Toshihiko,
aren't you?
Minoru is -
waiting for you.
Come with us,
Shall we?
No!
What are you doing there?
Are you OK?
Who the hell are they?
Minoru's back!
What happened, Minoru?
Who are they?
Tell me who they are!
I'm sorry.
I stole the negative.
I'm so sorry.
The End
PURIFICATION DOESN'T WORK
I wanted to work in the film industry.
I got a job with a film studio
prop department.
But there was a gap between
my ideals and reality.
The salary wasn't much and the work was hard.
Take that cigarette out of your mouth.
No one uses this crap nowadays.
That's not the point!
I'll wash it.
A prop is an actor's tool.
Each dress and prop has their own spirit.
So...you have to take good care of them.
I understand.
You'd better quit soon, too.
Is that...
Get rid of it.
Everybody's already gone so why...
The noise was from the shelf
where blood-stained armor lay.
Mr. Tadano.
Who are you?
Actor fatality on film set.
Was it this man?
I didn't see his face.
The budget was tight but they were ambitious.
The film industry was on a decline.
They were slacking.
They didn't pay out wages.
The staff gradually left one by one.
As did I.
All the armor was left on set.
Was that blood?
The device under his armor went off too soon.
He was still a young actor.
If only I were there.
I can't regret enough.
We must do a purification ceremony.
We've done it many times.
But...despite the ceremony and prayers,
The spirits wouldn't budge.
The props have souls.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to quit, too?
No.
I like films.
I won't quit. No matter what.
Ok.
Right.
After a short while, Tadano died.
He fell down a flight of stairs.
The End
OVERTIME (Part 1)
Can this make the deadline?
Shouldn't be any problem.
2 months ago,
Baba from PR was the first
Staff that did overtime on the
20th of the month are now missing
So this says
Self-immolation of an female employee
after ending affair with a younger man.
Please take care.
It's bullshit.
They all left
because they hated their jobs.
Mr. Shimotakaido.
Can you do overtime today?
Tonight?
You have a date tonight.
Yes, today is my girlfriend's birthday.
It must be hard to be a man.
She'd appreciate a hard worker.
It is just another birthday.
I'm sure she won't mind.
I've done it.
OK!
Thanks.
What's up? You weren't all here.
Shimako is nice, don't you think?
A real woman.
But that type of a woman can be daunting.
It doesn't matter.
She's like a big sister.
Surprised?
If you are to talk such crap,
you'll be eaten by an old woman.
Shimako could be such the lady.
Give me a break.
A rumor, nothing more.
It's just a rumor.
It's over. If work means more to you than me.
Then die!
I hate overtime.
Damn.
Hello, Accounting Department.
Hello.
Is this...
I was reading this earlier.
Hello.
Oh...
It's hot.
To Be Continued
OVERTIME (Part 2)
Your scream surprised me.
Why did you return to the office this late?
I forgot some papers I needed for tomorrow.
I'm going to drop them off
before coming here.
I see.
Did you think I was a ghost?
What?
That rumor?
When a young man works overtime by himself.
They bump into an old woman's ghost.
I could never say you are old.
Don't be nice to me.
Let's go home. It's deadline day tomorrow.
And I'm scared of ghosts
Wasn't your girlfriend upset?
Yes, she was furious.
I have to call her later to make it up to her.
Young women are a pain in the ass.
Don't be silly. They are only mannequins.
You're right.
I had a younger boyfriend quite sometime ago.
Did you?
He was fun.
I envy youth.
You're still young and attractive.
You think so?
Can you fall in love with an old lady like me?
Of course.
Then shall we go somewhere?
What?
Forget the girlfriend.
Well, but...
It's not good, Shimako.
Everybody will know.
And we do work in the same department.
You are sweating so much.
It's cold today.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You aren't thinking naughty thoughts, are you?
I'd never do such a thing in public.
In public?
Many people go in at the last floor.
This does not stop at this floor.
It's 5 past midnight.
On the 20th.
The deadline.
Shimako.
I ask you again.
Are you sure
you can fall for...
an old lady like me?
Can you fall for
Can you fall for me?
Tomorrow is the deadline.
It's going to be busy.
The End
SECOND ROUND
For hire
Central Hospital
Welcome!
Thanks! But that's what I should say.
I don't need old folks.
Money is money, I suppose.
Not for hire
Thank you.
Let's go!
When I was studying at Waseda
I was a team captain.
It was nothing special.
I was well-liked...
Despite being captain.
But being captain doesn't mean much but...
This is my card.
If your bed feels too cold, call me.
Of course you can call me tonight!
Oh, she's gone.
Where's the rest?
You freaked me out!
To the hospital!
To the hospital.
Ok.
Central Hospital
Welcome!
Sorry to surprise you.
I forgot something so I've come to pick it up.
See you soon.
Here comes my honey.
Left something behind?
Do get in.
You're cold.
Are you OK?
The taxi stand is crowded,
So I'll stop by the traffic circle.
Where's the hospital?
This is getting spooky. I better get home.
You can't escape.
The End
A WOMAN NEXT DOOR
This is where I used to live.
The old apartment attracted few tenants.
I lived there without any constraint.
And I liked it...
A family has dreams!
Cheers!
Oh, no! no!
Hey!
Hot...
Yes.
Could you keep the package for the next door?
I beg you.
Oh... OK.
Sorry...
Ok...
Yes.
Do you have a package for me?
Oh, yes.
That's mine.
Thank you.
That's heavy.
Hey.
Alright.
Huge!
Hey.
The End
MAI'S VOICE
The incident happened to Mr. Fujita.
After his only daughter Mai died and
He had just finished his 7th day of mourning.
Mai.
You'll get dizzy.
Mai!
It was the voice of his dead daughter.
I just heard things...
It was great
for Fujita to hear her voice.
Even it was only in his imagination.
It's not your imagination.
Mai!
Mai's Voice
Their daughter's death filled them with grief.
It tore the couples heart in 2.
It was painful.
Then one day...
Keep your chin up, Daddy.
Mai.
I'll be fine.
I'll do my best.
He discovered that he alone
could communicate with her.
Mr. Fujita?
Here is...
His mind was always elsewhere.
His wife worked at a bar.
But her customers couldn't console her.
You're over-filling.
She, too, began to hear Mai's voice.
One day,
Mr. Fujita visited his wife's bar.
You don't normally come here.
What are you wearing?
We're having a fancy dress party tonight.
It was organized by a regular customer.
We're doing this to cheer your wife up.
His colleague was there, too.
But it hardly raised his spirits.
He couldn't share their enthusiasm.
Mai, I'm on my own.
I can't forgive them.
Mai!
He couldn't see her.
But he could feel her presence.
He couldn't take anymore and left the bar.
Mr. Fujita!
Reiko...
I thought that was you.
He bumped
into Reiko, an old flame.
Out of regret or loneliness...
He drunk enough to forget his pain.
When he awoke he found himself in the hotel.
Oh, no!
Hello...
Could you wait a little?
Oh, no.
Mai?
What am I doing here?
Sorry to keep you waiting. Mr. Fujita?
His conscience forced him to return home.
I'm home.
Hello.
After my customers left the bar,
they were in a car accident.
3 of them!
What!
I heard...
Mai saying I can't forgive them.
Then, Fujita heard her...
You are dirty, Daddy.
That was the last they heard from Mai.
The End
THE PROMISE
Mine went further.
We were inseparable.
I was so happy to see her
that I enjoyed going visiting her.
Granny!
What Osamu?
Are you going to die one day?
Of course.
I've never seen a ghost.
Can you return as a ghost for me?
For you, I will.
I will come and see you
Really?
But you must promise me
not get frightened.
I won't.
You're my Granny.
Promise?
Yes.
I will return, you know.
I won't get frightened.
She died sometime ago.
I was sad but my only consolation
was she died without suffering.
Were you frightened?
I was dead scared.
Don't be frightened.
I was scared.
Shit! I was frightened.
Damn!
It was the 7th day of mourning.
I worked out a plan.
Her soul will return on the 49th day
before leaving for the next world.
I wouldn't be scared this time.
Granny, I'll challenge you.
Come on!
Why?
Granny didn't come after all.
Her soul must have come to rest.
Granddad!
The neighbors!
Did you get scared?
She'd got me.
Come the anniversary of her death...
I swear I wouldn't be scared.
The End
HE'S HOME
2 years ago, I met her at a bar
and I moved in.
Her husband passed away 3 years ago.
She lives at this apartment with her son Takeru.
At that time, I was in debt from
the failure of my company.
And didn't even have a place
to crash so I came here.
I wanted to sleep next to Tomoko.
But I didn't want to sleep
in front of her ex.
So I slept in the living room.
It was a lantern festival.
Her ex came back.
A year after from the day.
I was sleeping with her.
Ah... Daddy!
Daddy!
Are you ok?
What is wrong?
A year from the day...
I am still living with her.
Lantern festival is coming soon.
The End
THE BREATH OF MONONOKE
Exit. B1 Car park
The next bulletin is
before dawn today in subway in Shinjuku
young woman was found dead.
Her head, legs and arms were cut off
Police suspect that she could be
the latest victim of a serial killer...
Thanks.
Take care.
The victim Michiko Tachibana,
from Setagaya ward, was aged 27.
Exit D
Hello.
I can't pick up the phone right now.
Please leave a message.
I just arrived at the basement.
I'll be there shortly.
The next bulletin is
this afternoon in the underground
car park of the Hotel New Year
in Tokyo.
A body of a young woman
was discovered.
Police believe her to be
the latest victim.
They have increased efforts
to solve this case.
The victim is Mrs. Akemi Makimura
from Nerima ward.
Subtitle: Arigön
The End